<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Unity Editor Interface on The Guidebook</title>
    <link>http://guidebook.hdyar.com/docs/unity/unity-interface/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Unity Editor Interface on The Guidebook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://guidebook.hdyar.com/docs/unity/unity-interface/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adjusting Layouts</title>
      <link>http://guidebook.hdyar.com/docs/unity/unity-interface/layouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://guidebook.hdyar.com/docs/unity/unity-interface/layouts/</guid>
      <description>Adjusting Layouts and Customizing Unity #    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Game View</title>
      <link>http://guidebook.hdyar.com/docs/unity/unity-interface/game-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://guidebook.hdyar.com/docs/unity/unity-interface/game-view/</guid>
      <description>The Game View #  The game view is where we run our games. See the unity manual on the Game View.
First, our scene view camera and our game view camera are two completely separate things. The scene view, and its &amp;lsquo;camera&amp;rsquo; that you control with the mouse, is an editor tool. The camera&amp;rsquo;s location has no impact on the final, finished, game. The game view, then, allows us to see the games current actual state, how it will be rendered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hierarchy Window</title>
      <link>http://guidebook.hdyar.com/docs/unity/unity-interface/hierarchy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://guidebook.hdyar.com/docs/unity/unity-interface/hierarchy/</guid>
      <description>The Hierarchy #  The hierarchy window shows us a list of all of our GameObjects in a scene. It&amp;rsquo;s a one-dimensional view of the scene, represented as a list.   It also is where we can group GameObjects together by dragging and dropping them. This is called “parenting”. It’s not just a visual organizational tool, it can have a major impact on how objects in the scene behave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Scene View</title>
      <link>http://guidebook.hdyar.com/docs/unity/unity-interface/scene-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://guidebook.hdyar.com/docs/unity/unity-interface/scene-view/</guid>
      <description>The Scene View #  The Scene View, or Scene Window, is where we will spend the majority of our time in Unity. It allows us to see our scene, and edit and select objects.
While the scene view has been updated twice since these screenshots have been taken, in different versions of Unity, the buttons have moved around. In 2021.1 most of the tools are now inside of, or along the top of, the scene window itself.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
